(Past Leonard:)You might be an expert on theoretical
physics and science fiction programs...
(Past Leonard:)...and where to sit on a freaking couch,
but this is applied physics.
And when it comes to applied physics--
Uh-oh.
(Past Howard:)-What's happening?
-A bad thing. A very bad thing.
(Past Leonard:)Get the door.
Get the door. Get the door. Get the door.
(Past Howard:)-You're waiting for the elevator?
-Oh, right.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
(Past Raj:)-Wait. It's here.
-Ah!
(Past Sheldon:)Give me that.
(Past Leonard:)What'd you do that for?
I had plenty of time.
[EXPLOSION]
(Past Sheldon:)You're welcome.
(Leonard:)Not only did Sheldon save my life,
he didn't rat me out to the landlord.